(Leonard:)Your psychic didn't tell you
I was going to be a jerk?
Heh, heh. Bite me.
(Leonard:)-Come on, Penny.
-Why don't you kids go ahead and chat?
(Howard:)We're gonna make out back here.
(Bernadette:)I'm sliding into third.
(Raj:)Thanks for coming with me.
(Sheldon:)Thanks for giving me your limited edition
Green Lantern lantern.
(Raj:)Did you really have to bring it
with you?
(Sheldon:)What if evil strikes
and my power ring runs low?
(Raj:)-Come on, let's get a drink.
-I don't drink.
(Raj:)Well, I do.
(Raj:)And when my wingman is carrying
a Green Lantern lantern, I drink a lot.
(Raj:)I'll have a screwdriver, please.
And don't be chintzy with the screw.
I would like a root-beer float.
(Raj:)-Sheldon, they don't have ice cream.
-They don't?
(Sheldon:)Well, apparently these people and I
differ greatly on the definition of "party."